[{"answer": "One could pray ...", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "But you actually expected Zimmerman to learn something from this?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Well, I do think he's a victim of his own stupidity at this point.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "... can you construct for me any form of rational defense for the way Zimmerman is currently behaving?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well, I really don't think God and Jesus really want to be dragged into George Zimmerman's tweeting with you.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Then told this is about God, did he find God after he shot Trayvon Martin and before he pulled the shotgun on his girlfriend or had a fight with his wife.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Yeah, Nancy?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Let me finish.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "But he's still a killer isn't it?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Nancy, you're not -- you're totally leaving out the core part of what the jury and thank goodness you weren't on that jury because they looked at the facts and you don't want to deal with the fact that there was a ...", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Well, a lot of people suggest that it's a Florida issue.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Is it an American societal or cultural issue, what is it?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "... I wouldn't if she -- I'm unarmed person and I would've be out at that time of night trying to find another black youth to get arrested, you know, he knew he wasn't supposed to be out with a gun, that was a rule of neighborhood watch.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "... that woman and they'll be dirty on the ground?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "OK, Van Jones, Van Jones.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "What a surprise?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "I think that there -- there's a couple of things here.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Is there though a racial element to these two stories which links them?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "I do believe...", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "... all right?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Let's get your reaction as you were talking in the break there about this Michael Dunn case?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "I find Dunn's account to be incredible.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "And we've got these two cases not dissimilar where people have (inaudible) and the option of it is two 17-year old kids have been shot dead?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Nancy Grace, can we, you know, she drives about gun control then.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "So, it makes me wonder, did the prosecution overcharge should this have been a man slaughter case?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Well, I think the NRA has been too successful.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "How do you change that impulsive thing?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "MERCONISH: Well, it has an impact for us.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Does it really have any impact on them?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know that he's going to get credit for the legacy from half of the electorate because half of the electorate as you well know has drawn a line in the sand and regardless of which way this thing goes.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "What would constitute a great legacy outside of ObamaCare for Obama?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "You know, it depends, if there's anything, if there's one shred of evidence, if there's one witness, if there's one e-mail out there that contradicts what he said at that marathon press conference then he's finished.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Do you think he can come through with all this stuff (ph)?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "You know, I don't think that Rand Paul can lay claim to the Christie constituency.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "What about Rand Paul that we mentioned earlier?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "I don't -- Piers, I don't think so.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "But could Rand Paul rally the core base of the party perhaps better than Chris Christie?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Well, thank God you're not asking me about Abigail Adams.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "What do we think of Michelle Obama?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "No, you're not wrong whatsoever, Piers.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Am I wrong to do that?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Obviously, not at all please, Piers.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Is he horrified about the content, what do you think?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I absolutely do, Piers and so if anything good has going to come from this, it's going to be that usually for any kind of major change to come.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Do you think that this may draw a better line in the sand about where bonds (ph) begins and ends and genuine harassment and abused and bullying stops?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Well, definitely and I think its going to be a really positive situation moving forward.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "So, do you think it will have a big effect on people and how they're looking at this case now when they actually see this report as this come out?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Well, Piers I'm not going to get into that.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "Does he blame himself at all for, perhaps, encouraging the bond to a certain point?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Well, I mean that's a great question.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "I'm sure everyone is having this debate in the NFL now about how you try and take these guys you on the pitch, you want to be after murderous barbarians and metaphorically speaking and then away from the pitch to be polite, gentle people?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Well, right now the Miami Dolphins have its rights.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Have you had offers some other teams?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "You know, that's not for me to say.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Should Richie Incognito be given another chance?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "UCKERMAN: Well, Piers as you know, I'm not a health professional but he sounds great, he sounds positive.", "docId": "140217pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Do you think it wouldn't take a bit more time?", "qSentId": 622}]